The final thing to do is make it to my backyard.
It can be damaged if we open up our.
BP.
In some free space.
If we right click or lock for event, any damage event, any damage will get them out to my player house
and we'll subtract it by the amount of damage that they took.
So hopefully it's up here.
Then we'll tell the game.
That is our new health, so our Dragon health and set it.
Then in order to make sure our placard accurately shows now that we now have, I am going to trek up
here and look for for loop.
And for the last index of this, we basically want to get the amount of damage that we've taken and
look for communicate.
This will convert it into an integer and hook this up to loss index.
On the first index, we just want to change this from one because arrays are counting from the number
zero and for how many damage I took, I'm going to drag in my HUD reference.
And called the damage or however many damage my player character took.
So if I hook up, nobody to hear.
And then just to quickly test this out in some free space, I'm going to right click and look for one.
And when I press the one button, I'm going to apply damage.
And I'm going to play damage to myself, so I'll drag up in myself.
Whoops.
So drink up here and look for self.
Get reference to.
So on the base damage, let's change this to be one and forget, play and go play.
I have four hearts, but press one.
One of them is removed.
If I press one again, the second one will be removed.
And let's just test that.
This works for multiple damage.
If I put two here.
I could compile and I could play to how it should be removed.
So I press one too hot, too removed.
So with that, we set up a system where we can remove our hearts.